{
    "id": "2e67368c516245cb8b5eb588c1b6c5dd",
    "title": "At, Or, In",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I saw a beautiful girl ………………… the shop.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c554a25c823a4cad83800f8cfdecbf2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met her ………………. a party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aa41dbd0f9844e8197977fc3080e5f2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a spelling mistake …………………. line nine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6c8e3e577d304ff1872c45b4a559e675"
        },
        {
            "question": "He works ………………….. the US.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af1fc6d540554b429f4022449bb095c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Grandmother is arriving ………………… the 30 train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f751f3eed99b4e969b8dd4a850dda892"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a student …………………. Cambridge.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ac5d5a4b5ab84b028957249fda40f867"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that pretty girl …………………. the second row?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7dcac37bef8c41ebb32ee619ee79f05b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat is ………………. the piano.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1d23b0aa3a64411390236c634992196d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why do you wear that ring ………………… your index finger?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "af4ca79205714f02a66e3f021cf6d6db"
        },
        {
            "question": "Eat ………………. the Modern Restaurant. They serve the best food in town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "de714d7fea344b01b45bb649a48619ed"
        }
    ]
}